aspiration.com 2017-09-30

# Privacy Policy | Aspiration

**Aspiration is a company built on trust. We gather customer information because it’s the law or because it helps us serve you. We will never sell your personal information for any reason. Read the details below:**

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. This notice informs you of the privacy policies of Aspiration Partners, Inc., Aspiration Fund Adviser, LLC (“Aspiration”) and the investment funds it manages. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.

Aspiration gathers information from its customers in the course of its operations. This privacy policy delineates how Aspiration handles personal information when users access our site. Further policies may govern information concerning specific products accessed by clients.

All users who access our site become users pursuant to Aspiration’s Privacy Policy and Terms of Use and thereby signify their acceptance of said policies and terms.

### Client Information

Aspiration collects and maintains information provided by and related to our clients so that we may provide our clients products and services. The types of personal information we collect and share depends on the product or service you have with us. This information can include but is not limited to: client social security number, assets, retirement assets, transaction history, checking account information, security purchase history, account balances, account transactions, and wire transfer transactions.

### We Limit Sharing of Personal Information

Federal regulations and industry and partner mandates require the collection of certain nonpublic information without which Aspiration services and products may not be available.

We will share your nonpublic information with certain third-party service providers as permitted and required by law in order to deliver our products and services to you. Aspiration and certain third-party service providers may use personal nonpublic information for reasons that include but are not limited to: account opening and validation; to comply with federal, state and local statutes; to process transactions; to send information to clients and client-related parties; to improve Aspiration services; to protect the security and integrity of our businesses, properties, affiliates, and clients; and to respond to legitimate and legal requests from governmental authorities or in connection with other legal proceedings. Third party-service providers may include, but are not limited to, fund accountants, custodians, transfer agents, client selected charities, and accounting firms. Such sharing may not be limited. 

### Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Non-public, but non-personally identifiable information, regarding Aspiration’s current and potential clients, including but not limited to demographic, geographic, or aggregated client information, can be used by Aspiration for any purpose.

### Safeguards

Aspiration stores and maintains data with physical and electronic safeguards that comply with federal law. We limit access to user and customer data to the extent possible to those employees with authorized access, and take other measures to protect client information which include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. Our service providers are held accountable for adhering to strict policies and procedures to prevent any misuse of your nonpublic personal information.

We use our reasonable best efforts to protect user information however no method of transmission or method of data storage is 100% secure. Despite our commercially reasonable efforts, we cannot assure that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this policy. 

Your use of the Aspiration platform acknowledges that Aspiration is not liable or responsible for any intercepted information and you hereby release Aspiration from any and all claims arising out of or related to an unauthorized or inadvertent breach of data or violation of privacy policies.

### Information Posted to the Aspiration Platform

Aspiration is not responsible for any user information shared in public forums such as blogs, chats, videos or social media. Aspiration retains full, irrevocable, royalty-free, worldwide sublicensable, and perpetual intellectual property rights around any user-generated content uploaded, shared, transmitted, or otherwise publicly disseminated on the Aspiration site. Aspiration can store, use, reproduce, modify, and adapt such content and will retain full rights to any derivative works or compilations of such content. Users warrant by their actions that they have the necessary rights to grant such licenses to Aspiration. Aspiration can further delete such content at any time and for any reason.

Aspiration has no obligation to monitor or ability to control the information users publicly place on our Platform. We do not endorse any opinion, recommendation, and information that is expressed in this fashion. By accessing the Platform, users waive any rights or remedies against Aspiration in relation to such data.

### Tracking

While you are on Aspiration’s platform, and other websites, online ad networks we work with may place anonymous cookies on your computer, and use similar technologies, in order to understand your interests based on your (anonymous) online activities, and thus to tailor more relevant ads to you. If you do not wish to receive such tailored advertising, you can visit this [page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of most companies that engage in such advertising. (This will not prevent you from seeing ads; the ads simply will not be delivered through these targeting methods.)

### Contact Information and Opt Out

Clients can unsubscribe from marketing and otherwise informational emails from Aspiration and affiliated third parties utilizing your personal information, including your creditworthiness, on a forward-going basis by contacting Aspiration or clicking on an unsubscribe link.

Clients can also opt-out of having their information shared for marketing purposes on a forward-going basis with nonaffiliated third parties by contacting [privacy@aspiration.com](mailto:privacy@aspiration.com). We will endeavor to comply with such requests as quickly as commercially reasonably practicable.

Please note however that Aspiration clients cannot opt out of receiving administrative messages.

Any third party offering that our users or clients accede to will be governed by that party’s privacy and commercial policies.

Aspiration may, from time to time, recommend third-party service and product providers to its clients. In such cases, we will only share personally-identifiable client information with said parties if our clients indicate an express interest in learning more.

Aspiration is not geared toward anyone under the age of 18. We will endeavor to delete in a time and manner that is commercially reasonable personally identifiable information provided by minor children without their parent’s or guardian’s consent upon notification by said parent or guardian at privacy@aspiration.com. We are not liable for the consequences of such information having been shared with Aspiration.

Aspiration is not responsible for the privacy, security, or information policies of third party links from or on the Aspiration site.

Privacy policies may change from time to time. Notification of such changes will occur on this page and/or in an email notification.

We will retain personally identifiable nonpublic information for the period necessary for Aspiration’s business and legal requirements unless such information is required or allowed to be held for a different period by law.

Please direct any questions to [privacy@aspiration.com](mailto:privacy@aspiration.com) or [800-683-8529](tel:800-683-8529).
